Guide to the Alan Sondheim Papers MSS.267
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Written Work
  - "Nicaragua", Undated (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - "Night -- On Saying Goodby to the Country", 1963 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - "Nightclub", Undated (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - "Nine Short Poems Influenced By the Spanish", Undated (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - "Noche", Undated (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - "Noise Culture", Undated (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - "Noise Culture: Art and Society in the Third Millennium", 1992 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - "Noise Culture," Art Press, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - "The Noise of the Future: Crumbling Cities and Universal Dreams", Undated (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - "No Longer", Undated (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - "No Nietzsche's Eternal Recurrance: The Same Old Story", Undated (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - "Noosw w (The Poster Piece)", Undated (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - "North North Dallas Texas North", Undated (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - "No Sleep Empty Apartment Leaving, Suture, Cauterization…", 1982 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - "Notations", Undated (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - "Note on Assimilation Schema", 1972 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Notebook, Undated (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Notebooks, Undated (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - "The Notebook: Work on the Run from Fall 1977" (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - "Notes for Talk", Undated (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - "Notes from the Sketchbook", Undated (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - "Notes on a Program for the Topology of Intention", Undated (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - "Notes on a Series of Videotapes Concerned with Positioning", Undated (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - "Notes on Business Hierarchies," Meta Ltd., Undated (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - "Notes on Coding and Symmetry", Undated (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - "Notes on Disaster (1972 Flood Wilkes-Barre/Kingston, Pennsylvania)," Meta Ltd. (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - "Notes on Film", 1979 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - "Notes on Futurology", Undated (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - "Notes on International Unemployment", Undated (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - "Notes on Landscape", Undated (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - "Notes on Marx, Etc.", Undated (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Notes on Readings, Undated (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - "Notes on Reductivism, Etc.", Undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - "Notes on Set Theory", Undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Notes on Sondheim's Work, Undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - "Notes on the Mechanisms of Secrecy", Undated (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - "Notes on the Mode of Organism", Undated (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - "Notes Related to BCL Research", Undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - "Nothing but the Thing", Undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - "Novena", Undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - "Now I Write…", Undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - "Numbers", Undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - "Obligatory Disclaimers", Undated (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - "Occurrence, Event Situation", Undated (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - "Okay. That This is the One on Objects. That This is the One on Objects and Slipping. That This is on What Bothers Me.", Undated (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - "On a Discussion With Clark Coolidge", Undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - "On a Morning in Chicago", Undated (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - "On a Particular Mythic Conception", Undated (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - "On Assertion," Meta Ltd., Undated (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - "On Certain Remarkable Occurances", Undated (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - "On Drawing -- A Rhetoric", 1976 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - "One Speaks", Undated (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - "One Two", 1983 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - "On Her Leaving", Undated (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - "On Human Destructiveness", Undated (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - "On Inscription and Assertion in Relation to Relativized Null Sets", Undated (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - "On Machines", Undated (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - "On Painting", Undated (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - "On Quitting Music", Undated (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - "On Returning From Abroad: The Omens", Undated (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - "On Seeing the Longest Day", Undated (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - "On That Very Uncomfortable Edge: An Interview With Alan Sondheim," Arts Journal, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - "On the African Finger Piano," Brown Daily Herald, January 12 1966 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - "On the Error of Typing", 1984 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - "On the Inherent Transparency of the Material World", Undated (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - "On the Notebooks of Leonardo Da Vinci", Undated (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - "On the Phenomenology of Artificial Intelligence and Program Space", 1983 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - "On the Publication of Disorders of the Real, Undated (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - "On the Written in Relation to the Spoken", 1976 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - "On This Writing", Undated (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - "On Turbulence", Undated (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - "On Writing 'The Demolition of the Avant-Garde' ", Undated (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - "Opinions Give The Political Show Potence," The Atlanta Journal, June 24, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - "Orange County California and the Economics of Language", Undated (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - "Or a Portrait", Undated (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - "Orders of the Real", 2005 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_12, Box 46, Folder 42)
  - "The Other Land", Undated (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - "The Others: Essays on the Imaginable", Undated (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - "Our Border Incident", Undated (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - "Our Own Border Incident", Undated (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - "The 'Our Experiment' ", Undated (Box 46, Folder 47)
  - "Outlaw Intellectualism: Natural Hermeneutics and Notes on Mechanisms of Secrecy I", 1977 (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - "(Outline) Fabrication of a Culture: The Signature", Undated (Box 46, Folder 49)
  - "Over Arizona", Undated (Box 46, Folder 50)
  - "Paen", Undated (Box 46, Folder 51)
  - "Pain and Decadance - Dedicated to Huysmans", Undated (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - "The Painting", Undated (Box 46, Folder 53, 54)
  - "(Painting ( or: ( or:: ( The Writing About Painting", Undated (Box 46, Folder 55)
  - "Painting A x B", Undated (Box 46, Folder 56)
  - "Parataxis", Undated (Box 46, Folder 57)
  - "Part I. Time Symmetry and Acausality", Undated (Box 46, Folder 58)
  - "Part 3, The Fitfull Escapade", Undated (Box 46, Folder 59)
  - "Partial Summarization/Ideology of the Media", Undated (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - "Part-Objects", Undated (Box 46, Folder 61)
  - "Party Fragment", Undated (Box 46, Folder 62)
  - "Pathology", Undated (Box 46, Folder 63)
  - "Penumbra/Grey", Undated (Box 46, Folder 64)
  - "The Permanent Theses", Undated (Box 46, Folder 65)
  - "Pessimism", Undated (Box 46, Folder 66)
  - "The Phenomenology and Function of Short-Wave," Ear Magazine, March 1984 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - "Phenomenology of the Bourgeois Home", Undated (Box 46, Folder 67)
  - "Phenomenology of the Signature, Whiteman in the Mid-U.S.", 1978 (Box 46, Folder 68)
  - "The Philosophy of Mystery", Undated (Box 46, Folder 69)
  - "Philosophy" Web Narrative, 2006 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_13)
  - "The Photographs", Undated (Box 47, Folder 1, 2)
  - "Photography", Undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - "Photography and Reality", Undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - "Photography, Angles and Mappings", Undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - "Photophobia", Undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - "The Physics and Psychology of Time", 1972 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - "Place-Names: Confessions of an Exile", 1989 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - "Plant", Undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - "Play 2", Undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - "Play 3", Undated (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - "Play Called Air", Undated (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - "Pleistocene", Undated (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - "PMS (Post-Modern Syndrome)", Undated (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - "Poem Hours", 1970 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - "Poem or 25", Undated (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - "Poem, Out, Line", 1969 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - "Poem to Susan", Undated (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - "The Poem Which Accompanies the Writing", Undated (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Poems by Charles Glass, Undated (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - "[Poetic Language: Linguistic Measure.]", 1971 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - "Point, Line, Cusp, Etc.", 1980 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Political Activism, Undated (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - "The Politics of Discourse/ Discourse of Politics", 1984 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - "Polymorphous Perverse Description", Undated (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - "Pornography, Its Penis, Its Vagina", 1981 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - "Portrayal", Undated (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - "Position Paper For Public Domain: Global Identity/Technology Project", Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - "The Possibility of a Neutralizing Machine", Undated (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - " 'Postmodernist Aesthetics'-- Notes", Undated (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - "Potential of the Body", Undated (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - "Precis", Undated (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - "Premise", Undated (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - "The Presence of the Filmmaker, the Presence of the Film", Undated (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - "Presence of Future Presence of Video," Art Vu, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - "Presence: To Susan", Undated (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Press Coverage of Sondheim's Work, 1970-2008 (Box 47, Folder 37, 38, 39, 40)
  - "Presupposition of Non-Determination", Undated (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - "Prevarications", Undated (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - "The Principle of the Fragility of Good Things", Undated (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - "Principles of First Philosophy", 1991 (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - "(Print)," Meta, Ltd., Undated (Box 47, Folder 45)
  - "Problematics of Noise", Undated (Box 47, Folder 46)
  - "Problème Posé Par Une Sculpture", 1972 (Box 47, Folder 47)
  - "Proem", 1980 (Box 47, Folder 48)
  - "Prolog", Undated (Box 47, Folder 49)
  - "Proof is in the Pudding", Undated (Box 47, Folder 50)
  - "Proposal for an Interactive Children's Program on Cable Television", 1976 (Box 47, Folder 51)
  - "Proposal for Art Papers", Undated (Box 47, Folder 52)
  - "Psychology", Undated (Box 47, Folder 53)
  - "Psychosis", Undated (Box 47, Folder 54)
  - Publication Sales, Undated (Box 47, Folder 55)
  - Published Articles - Digital Copies and Drafts, 1999-2010 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_31)
    These files are digital copies and drafts of articles published in magazines and journals such as "Art papers" and "Millennium Film Journal."
  - Published Reviews - Digital Copies and Drafts, 2001-2010 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_32)
    These files include digital copies and drafts of published reviews. Alan Sondheim often reviewed books, films, electronics, and exhibits.
  - "Quadrant Supervisor", Undated (Box 47, Folder 56)
  - "The Qualms of Substance and Death", Undated (Box 47, Folder 57)
  - "Quotations", Undated (Box 47, Folder 58)
  - "Raise", Undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - "Randy--", Undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - "Real Life Questions", Undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - "Recognition of Entities", Undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - "Reel 3", Undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - "Relation of the Body", 1982 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - "The Relevance of Movement in Philosophy", Undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - "Replacement Reading and the Seal of Approval", Undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - "Representation", Undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - "Representation of the Fundamental Rule", Undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - "The Representation of Women", Undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - "Reproduction Piece", Undated (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - "Rereading Disorders of the Real", Undated (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - "Resemblances and the Absent", Undated (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - "Resistance/Against the Text", Undated (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - "Resonances", 1971 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - "Review and Interview with Ravi Shankar," Brown Daily Herald, December 6 1967 (Box 77, Folder 32)
  - Reviews, Undated (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - "Rewhence", Undated (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - "Rewrite of Template Module", Undated (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - "Robbed Texts, Immobilization", 2000 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - "Rug 'Rug' Wall [ ]", 1969 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - "S--------grad", Undated (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - "S8," Image News, August 1987 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - "S.A. (Paysage)", Undated (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - "Sad Pastorale", Undated (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - "The Same", Undated (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - "Sampling Everyone", Undated (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - "San Francisco", Undated (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - "Scab/Coagulation/Clot", 1982 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - "Schemata of Transform Fine-Structures from the Fundamental Rule", 1977 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - "School of Fiction", Undated (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - "Science and Art: In Terms of Normal Activity.", Undated (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - "Sealing", Undated (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - "Seattle", Undated (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - "Second Gear", Undated (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - "Second Look", 1980 (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - "Secret/code", Undated (Box 48, Folder 37)
  - "The Seen of it All", Undated (Box 48, Folder 38)
  - "Self/Ego/Simulacrum", Undated (Box 48, Folder 39)
  - "Self-Evident Points on Regionalism", Undated (Box 48, Folder 40)
  - "Self-Immersion", Undated (Box 48, Folder 41)
  - "Self-Indulgence", Undated (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - "Self-Portrait", Undated (Box 48, Folder 43)
  - "The Sensorium", 1984 (Box 48, Folder 44)
  - "Sentencing/Death", 1985 (Box 48, Folder 45)
  - "Separation, Beth", Undated (Box 48, Folder 46)
  - Sequence 3 (Sequence 1 and 2), Burning Deck, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 47)
  - "Seri", Undated (Box 48, Folder 48)
  - "The Series Which Empties Itself of Place, But Extends by an Expansion of Air", Undated (Box 48, Folder 49)
  - "Serrated Edges", 1970 (Box 48, Folder 50)
  - "Setting", Undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - "Seventy-four Characteristics of the World", 1975 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - "Sexing", Undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - "Sexing Short-Circuit", Undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - "The Sexual Image", 1982 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - "Sexualities, Bindings, Cauterizations, Incandescent Texts", Undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - "Shaman", Undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - "Shamanic", Undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - "Shamanism", Undated (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - "Shamanism and the Flesh of the World", Undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - "Shark Attack", July 1982 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - "The Shattering of Worlds", Undated (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - "She Rises", Undated (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - "The Shifty Character in the Kind of Poem That", Undated (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - "Shoreline", Undated (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - "Short-Circuit", Undated (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - "Shtetl", Undated (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - "The Sickness", 1985 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - "Sight: The Recent Work of Marcia Resnick", Undated (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - "Silent Scenarios: Titles", Undated (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - "Singularities", Undated (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - "Skelton in the Closet", Undated (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - "Skitch", Undated (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - "Skull", Undated (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - "Sleazy", Undated (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Sleazy and the Year 3000, Debrisfilm, 1987-1989 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - "Sleazy, Vulgar, Tawdry, Kitsch", Undated (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - "Snapshot", Undated (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - "Snow", Undated (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - "Soho", Undated (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - "Solar Archaeology", 1970 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - "Some Countries", Undated (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - "Some Differences Between Film and Television", Undated (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - "Some Notes on the Block and Diplomatic Language", Undated (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - "Some Notes on Vacuity", Undated (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - "Someone Else", Undated (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - "Someone Just Cited a Jew Again", Undated (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - "Some Statements on Autopornography", Undated (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - "Some Statements on the Phenomenology of Program Space (Phenomenology of Technology)", Undated (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - "Some Texts, Some, in Relation to a Film", Undated (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - "Some Theoretical Concerns", Undated (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - "Somethin' by the Windmill Selm", Undated (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - "Somewhat a Filmscript", Undated (Box 49, Folder 42)
  - "So Neural", Undated (Box 49, Folder 43)
  - "Sondheim Explains Film Povera," Image, March 1985 (Box 77, Folder 31)
  - "Song", Undated (Box 49, Folder 44)
  - "Sophia", 2004 (Box 49, Folder 45)
  - "The Space and the Time", Undated (Box 49, Folder 46)
  - "Sparks Take it Down", Undated (Box 49, Folder 47)
  - "S.P.E. Saturday, October 15, 11 AM, 1988" (Box 49, Folder 48)
  - "Speaking Sex", Undated (Box 49, Folder 49)
  - "Spidee", Undated (Box 49, Folder 50)
  - "Spinthariscope", Undated (Box 49, Folder 51)
  - "Splines of Information Wash Up Against the Debris Left by Text", Undated (Box 49, Folder 52)
  - "Spoliation", Undated (Box 49, Folder 53)
  - "Square", Undated (Box 49, Folder 54)
  - "Squaredance", Undated (Box 49, Folder 55)
  - "Squeaky Wheel", 1987 (Box 49, Folder 56)
  - "The Squealer!", 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 57)
  - "Standardized Introduction to the Film(s)", Undated (Box 49, Folder 58)
  - "State of the Art/Art of the State", 1987 (Box 49, Folder 59)
  - "Statements on Theory", Undated (Box 49, Folder 60)
  - "Status of the Dreams, Some Dreams, Fevers", Undated (Box 49, Folder 61)
  - "Stereo", Undated (Box 49, Folder 62)
  - "(Stereo) (Stereo) (Stereo)", 1984 (Box 49, Folder 63)
  - "Stolen Poem", Undated (Box 49, Folder 64)
  - "Story", Undated (Box 49, Folder 65)
  - "The Stress", 1984 (Box 49, Folder 66)
  - "Structure III", Undated (Box 49, Folder 67)
  - "The Structure of a Theory of Cultural Formations and the Social", Undated (Box 49, Folder 68)
  - "Structures of Belief", Undated (Box 49, Folder 69)
  - The Structure of Reality, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 70, Box 50, Folder 1, 2, 3)
  - The Structure of Reality: Evidence of a Theory and Appropriation, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - The Structure of Reality Text Plus Appendices, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - "Studio Problems: 2nd Session", Undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - "Style", Undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - "Subculture Taxonomy", Undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - "Subjectivity and Objectivity", Undated (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - "Subobj", Undated (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - "Sucking-the-Thumb and its Inversion as Inscription", 1976 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - "Suicide", Undated (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - "Suicide Piece; Kill Piece", Undated (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - "Suislawan Text", Undated (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - "Supplement: Irresolution of New Communications Orders", Undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - "Supplication and Waiting", Undated (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - "Swansong", Undated (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - "Swollen", Undated (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - "The Swollen Fissure of Painting", Undated (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Syntactical and Semantic Programming, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Syntactical and Semantic Programming, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - "The System of Inscriptions", Undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - "Systemics of Accumulations", Undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - "Tamerlane", Undated (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - "Tangential", Undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - "Tao" by Reiner Strasser and Alan Sondheim, 2004 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_14)
    "Tao" is an interactive cinematographic Flash piece, created in collaboration between Alan Sondheim and Reiner Strasser. The musical compositions, which consist of modified shakuhachi, and short video components are by Alan Sondheim.
  - "Tasmanian Punks at the Nowhere Club", Undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - "The Tasmanian Work", Undated (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - "Teen Angel's", Undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - "The Telegram From a Conceivable Site of War", Undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - "Television Piece", 1970 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - "Template Matching for Binary Codes", Undated (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - "Testimony of Love and Death", Undated (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - "Texas", Undated (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Texas Instruments Program Submissions, Undated (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - "(Text)", 1983 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - "Textbook of Thinking", 1991 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Text Files - Poetry, Prose, Notes, and Working Files, 1994-2010 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_33)
  - "Texts" by Alan Sondheim and Geralyn Donahue, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - "Text to Accompany Recent Films", Undated (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - "Text/Vide: Word Fence", Undated (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - "That 'Self' That 'Thing' is 'Not' ", Undated (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - "Theorem", 1988 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - "Theoretical Work Stemming from The Structure of Reality Reintegrated into Marxist Theoretical Levels", 1978 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - "Theory", 1983 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - "The Theory that Swallowed the World", Undated (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - "Theory of Video", Undated (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - "Them", 1984 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - "The Themes in my Work and its Project", Undated (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - "The Wallpapyr Poems", Undated (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - "There is No One.", 1982 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - "Theses About Jews", Undated (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - "Theses on the Inversion of the Cinema," Millennium Film Journal, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - "This Cutting Work", Undated (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - "This is All That Can Be Said", Undated (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - "This is How the Film Goes", Undated (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - "This Night of Beautiful Magic", Undated (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - "This Space, Peering Out", Undated (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - "This Way Acconci", Undated (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - "Thomas Chatterton: Introduction to the Notes", 1983 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - "Though", Undated (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - "Those", Undated (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - "The Three Protactions of a New Philosophy", 1990 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - "(Three Short Texts)", Undated (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - "Throat," Art Papers, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - "Tmo Erotic Filws", 1980 (Box 51, Folder 43)
  - "To", Undated (Box 51, Folder 44)
  - "To Carol", Undated (Box 51, Folder 45)
  - "To Energize Such a Word", 1984 (Box 51, Folder 46)
  - "To Locate/ To Cross Over", Undated (Box 51, Folder 47)
  - "Tomb", Undated (Box 51, Folder 48)
  - "To Munch", Undated (Box 51, Folder 49)
  - "Toni 8", Undated (Box 51, Folder 50)
  - "To Nira", Undated (Box 51, Folder 51)
  - "Too Late Assassinate", Undated (Box 51, Folder 52)
  - "Torturous Justification", 1972 (Box 51, Folder 53)
  - "The Totality of Painting", Undated (Box 51, Folder 54)
  - "Touch and Caress the Beautiful Boundaries of Lipstick on Earth", Undated (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - "Towards a Bibliography", Undated (Box 51, Folder 56)
  - "Towards the Field", Undated (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - "Towards the Fourth Millennium", Undated (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - "Towards a Primary Differentiation Between Film and Video", 1986 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - "Towards a Primary Differentiation Between Film and Video", 1989 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - trAce Online Writing School Residency - Works and Correspondence, 1994-2004 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_34, Box 52, Folder 5)
  - "Trait", Undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - "Transcriptions + Annotations", Undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - "Transcription From Second Typing Session", Undated (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Translation "From Rafael Alberti: 'Si Mi Voz Muriera en Tierra' ", Undated (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - "Translation", Undated (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Translations of Poems by Federico Garcia Lorca, Undated (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - "Transmission", 1978 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - "Trivial Consequences: Death and Material in the Work of Elma Johnson", Undated (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - "Truth", Undated (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - "Truth", Undated (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - "Truth Emerging in the Hottest Summer", Undated (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - "Turbulence", Undated (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - "Twenty-First Century Script", Undated (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - "Twine. Line.", Undated (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - "Two Circles", Undated (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - "Two Early Poems to Janet", Undated (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - "Two (Four) Views of Niagara", 1979 (Box 52, Folder 22)